Chhavi Lakra

> Contact No: 9278002121

> Email: chhavilakra34@gmail.com

> Address: A-104, Shoe Market, Uttam Nagar, New Delhi – 59

Professional Summary

➤ Goal oriented, determined and focused with excellent communication skills. Highly proficient in HR compliance and process having experience of **4 years** with one of the most reputed companies in the compliance sector.

Key Skills & Competencies

Software & Tools	Microsoft word, Microsoft Excel, Power Point & Company Compliance Software such as ACT portal.
Languages	English & Hindi
os	Windows

Work Experiences

People Strong Pvt Ltd.

Duration	April-2023-Current
Designation	Specialist Compliance
Domain	Compliance & Process
Project overview	PF, ESI & PT challan process implementation. Labor law compliance act implementations and execution of the laws.
Tool Used	Microsoft Word, Microsoft PowerPoint and Word.
Responsibilities	 Handling Inspections, Notices and Client at PAN India locations for different clients. Responsible for handling employee's query related to PF. Handling the audit related to labour laws. Responsible for maintaining all records and registers under Labour laws compliance policies. Responsible for preparing monthly PF, ESI, LWF and PT reports or challans Responsible for sharing complete risk analysis and compliance report with respective stakeholder.

•	Active participation in the pre-sales call for the new client
	enrollment assistance.

- Proficient in handling multiple compliance partner calls and review meetings.
- Complete ownership for the full structured cycle of compliance.

■ TBO Tek Limited (TBO.com)

Duration	April/2022-February2023	
Designation	Executive Compliance & Process	
Domain		
Project overview	PF, ESI & PT challan process implementation. Labor law compliance act implementations and execution of the laws.	
Tool Used	Microsoft Word, Microsoft PowerPoint and Word.	
Responsibilities	 Responsible for maintaining all records and registers under Labour laws compliance policies. Responsible for filing monthly PF, ESI and PT challans. Responsible for sharing complete risk analysis and compliance report with respective stakeholder. Proficient in handling multiple compliance partner calls and review meetings. Recruitment process alignment at the time of joining of new candidates. Awareness session provided to the lateral hires over PF and labour laws queries. 	

Mynd Integrated Solutions Private Limited

Duration	March/2020 – April/2022	
Designation	Associate Executive	
Domain	Compliance & Process	
Project overview	PF, ESI & PT challan process implementation. Labor law compliance act implementations and execution of the laws.	
Tool Used	Microsoft Word, Microsoft PowerPoint and Word.	
Responsibilities	 Responsible for maintaining all records and registers under Labor law compliance policies. Responsible for filing monthly PF, ESI and PT challans. Responsible for sharing complete risk analysis and compliance report with respective stakeholder. Proficient in handling multiple client calls and review meetings 	

Education

- Bachelor's in Commerce batch of (2014-2017) from Aditi Mahavidyalaya, Delhi University.
- 12th from CBSE Board in 2014.
- 10th from CBSE Board in 2012.

Certifications

• Certified in Tally ERP 9.

Extra-Curricular Activities

- Participate in Problem Solving Assessment (PSA) conducted by CBSE in 2013.
- Member of Leader of Tomorrow.